Ana-Louise Trinidad

Email: <u>anamtrinidad@outlook.com</u>

Portfolio: https://ana3nity.github.io/gaming-ux-portfolio/ LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ana-louise-trinidad/

> | Bay Area, CA | Phone: (408) 444-6771

My passion for gaming and user experience drives me to contribute my skills to this exciting industry. With a focus on critical thinking, I aim to develop solutions that improve the user experience for players, creating more engaging and enjoyable gaming experiences.

Technical Skills

UX/UI Design Tools: User Research, User Interviews, Problem Spotting, Critical Thinking, Site Maps, Affinity Diagrams, Storytelling, Empathy Development, Usability Testing, Visual Design

Technical: Figma, Notion, Trello, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, GitHub, Basic Unity, Visual Studio Code, Atom

Projects

Game Jam 2023 | UI/UX Designer

This Game Jam aimed to create a game in 12 days using HTML5. The game submission was completed by a 4 person team: Game Dev, UI/UX, Artist, and Audio.

- Skills | Technologies used: Figma, Flowchart, Wireframes, Prototyping, Mockups, communication with devs, UI style guide, creation of UI assets such as icons
- Link to Game Here

First-Person Shooter Feature Project | GRUX Case Study

The aim of this case study is to improve the surfacing of patch note information about weapons and abilities to casual, new, or returning online FPS players.

 Skills | Technologies Used: Proto-Persona, Competitive Analysis, User Flow, Wireframing and Prototyping, Usability Testing, Figma, Google Drive, screen video recorders

Public Utility County Website Redesign | UC Berkeley *UX/UI Bootcamp*

The aim of this project was to improve the usability and findability of new house owning users to start a water service on the county's website

 Skills | Technologies Used: Stakeholder Interviews, User Research (Interviews + Surveys) & Analysis, User Experience Design (UI/UX), Interaction Design, Prototyping, Usability Testing

Work Experience

Filipino Advocates for Justice

April 2022 - Present

Domestic Worker/Caregiver Outreach for Filipino Advocates for Justice & UX designer & Wordpress Front-End Developer

- Creating social media outreach materials on Canva
- Re-making old outreach materials such as membership forms, outreach physical flyers using Word Doc and Canva
- Developing infographic and social media materials for internal Trainings and educational outreach

Ohlone Community College Contact Tracer/Case Investigator for COVID-19

May 2021 - September 2021

- Conduct the initial investigation of possible exposures or positive COVID-19 cases and reports confirmed cases to Alameda Public Health Department and California Department of Public Health
- Develop training and presentation material and conduct trainings for faculty, staff, administrators and students on effective, contact tracing/case investigation

Volunteer

AAPI Women Lead Redesign Project User Researcher

April 2023 - June 2023

• User Research: Research Plan creation, User Survey creation, User interviewees, Affinity Diagram, Empathy Map, discovering User Persona, Stakeholder liaison, team management and collaboration

San Jose Peace and Justice Center Redesign & Develop Project March 2023 - June 2023 User Researcher Lead & Wordpress Front-End Developer

• User Research: Research Plan creation, distributed and recruited user interviewees via User Survey, conducted User interviewees, Affinity Diagram, Empathy Map, User

- Persona Creation, Site Map, Information Architecture, Stakeholder liaison, team management and collaboration
- Developed Mock-up with another Front-End Developer with HTML and CSS on Visual Studio Code
- Wordpress Front-End Developer: Implementation of High-Fidelity Prototypes

San Jose Strong; Web Dev Committee & App Dev Committee April 2023 - Present User Researcher & Front-End Developer

- User Researcher:
 - Creation of Internal Database User Survey, Usability Testing Plan, Script, and Ouestions
- Web Dev Committee roles:
 - Assigned a portion of the website building-process using Webflow
 - Developing parts of the website from referencing High-Fidelity prototypes from the web designer
- App Dev Committee roles:
 - Helping with portion of the San Jose Strong app with Front-End coding such as HTML, CSS, Javascript, React
 - Contribute in making improvements to the app by usability testing

Education

Certificate in UX/UI Design
University of California, Berkeley Extension

April 2023

Bachelor of Arts in General Biology San Francisco State University

May 2018